Hello hello
everyone welcome to my YouTube channel's
principal today is benefit rather news from our hobby
ICICI Lombard and Aditya
Birla Money is going to be blocked in the IAS Law Board
due to which some
decline can be seen in the stock and the same
bad news has come for Aditya Birla Money that SEBI has
imposed a fine of around one crore on them before moving forward if you have
not yet subscribed to the channel then please
motivate us by subscribing so first of all
if we talk about ICICI
Lombard then they had acquired
Bharti AXA General Insurance on 1st September this year
Bharti AXA
was a joint venture of Bharti Enterprises and
AXA which is a French insurance company
and in return of this
3 crore 58 lakh equity shares were issued to them
in which Bharti got 1 crore 82 lakh and 1
crore 75 lakh for one year the
investment holding company is Society and
John so now it is that Society and John which
if they have acquired Bharti's investment
holding  The company is selling its entire
share through a block deal.
In this, around 175 crores were issued to Joshi Arun,
which
makes up his share of around 3.85%. Take this and
later it is going to sell them today and its
price is believed that
it will sell these shares between 1497 to 1576.
If this deal happens around 1497, then the
total amount will be around 2620 crores
and if the deal on the higher side happens at 1575, then
it will be of 2759 crores, so
who will get the amount in between and if it happens
at 1497, which is believed that
most of the shares will be bought around 1497, then
it will be a five percent discount from yesterday's
closing. The one who is getting this deal done is
BNP Paribas, this is its
test and it can be seen that normally when a
block deal happens and it is
less than the current market price, then the share price goes towards  If it had
run away, you would probably see today that the
share of Lombard would have reached around 1500 for
once.
If we talk about our other company
which is in the news, Aditya Birla Money.
These days, the
time is not going well for Aditya Birla Group companies, be it
Vodafone or Grasim. Now it was the turn of
Aditya Birla Money, on whom SEBI has
imposed a fine of around Rs 1 crore 2 lakh
because it has not followed many market
norms and stock broker regulations.
It is a broking
company, apart from this it
also provides portfolio management services, so
this is the amount, they will have to pay the fine account in 45 days.
Why has this fine been imposed? Around March 2019,
some proceedings were started against their gangsters
by SEBI through
some dead sales and N initials like BSC 1st Year Depository
and they found that
they have some closes in their work. One,
they do
not sign an agreement for the portfolio management service which they provide to their clients.  Secondly, they do not
have a liquid system and inter-petrol.
When they deal with the line,
apart from that, they overstate the profits of their clients
and
understate the losses and provide them with false
statements. These
important effects are
hidden from their clients, such as clients keep investing according to the
strategy suggested by them
and they keep
getting brokerage and other charges.
Apart from this, it was also found that they do
not settle the points of inactive plants,
which they should
do according to the SEBI circular. Secondly, in the Know Your Client
system of the brokerage firm,
when they submit the data
of the clients, there was a delay in it.
Due to all these reasons, a fine of Rs 1 crore 2 lakh was imposed on them, due to which it is
possible that today
its shares may see a slight decline.
Now if we talk about whether Ash-Ash Long
Baat shares should be bought, then first of all, if
we look at its performance for one year, then
it has given a return of 21 per cent in one year
only in 2021.  If the current return is 3.68%, then
it has not given any special return
whereas in 2015 it has given tremendous return
and the reason for this is that it had fallen a lot in January as well,
after that when the second wave of Kuwait
came, a lot of clean cuts were seen in the health insurance they
provide
and it is believed
that the normal 1 year loans were
seen within just one quarter
due to which there was a huge impact on their profits
and if we talk about the
list of products made by Tip, then they
see its average price of 1672 which is
around 6% above the current price
and on the higher side they see the price of 9037 and on the lower side
around 1117
and if we talk about its peers then you
can consider its market capitalization as its peer New India Assurance
because they provide general insurance.
Bajaj has some other businesses as well, so
if we look at their valuations and
PROSOPs, then it seems very low at the present
time, although their returns are quite good.  It has
n't performed well in a year. It's a profitable company. Dale
Steyn has a neck nipple. If there's no
flaw or problem debt-wise, you should buy its shares. If it doesn't,
it hasn't performed well in a year.
If it falls by 5% today,
I think in my personal opinion, there's
definitely a chance the stock could be
acquired. Now, as Kuber is
recovering, the losses
they incurred last time in the health insurance sector wo
n't happen. Their profits will be better this
quarter. Apart from this,
awareness is increasing among people about health insurance
and other insurance products
because their perspective has changed due to Corbett, due to which
premium income is also increasing. Overall, the
coming quarter will be positive for withdrawal.
If a correction of around 5% is
seen today due to the block deal, then
according to me, it could be a good move.
If this phase falls, it can be
invested in want-end strategies.
Normally, after the block deal, there is hope for a gain of up to 5%.
That will be useful today, after that
it may fall further for a few days or
trend at the same price, but normally
after some time the stock comes back to its original price
but comes to the pre-block deal
price, so if it
falls by five percent then you can consider it.
If we talk about AB Money, then it has
shown a return of 45 percent in one year and if in the last three months
it has shown a positive return of 12%, then it is a
very small company whose
profit is around 15 crores and
if the market capitalization is seen then
its peers like Satya Se
Security or India Bulls Sound
Service or Angel Broking do
not stand anywhere in front of them. It is a very small
company, its valuation seems to be okay, the
returns are also okay, but such small
companies can be volatile,
their debt to equity ratio is quite heavy-handed, which is
not good at all, although
today it can see a big fall, the
news has come that a fine is going to be imposed on it, so
if you  If you have faith in this business then
you can also invest in it and take advantage of it.
Maybe it will come back to normal in the short term
but I think that it is not very small
so you should invest in it very thoughtfully.
Before ending this video, as always I will
give a disclaimer that if you
want to invest in it then you should do it only on the basis of your
financial advisor and father research.
Thank you so much for
watching my video and God bless you all.